Guide to the Pennsylvania Economy League Records, 1925-1985 AIS.1978.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Municipal Governments, 1929-1975; II.
  - New Kensington, "Why a New Campus for Pennsylvania State University at New Kensington", Unknown
  - New Kensington, "A Financial Analysis 1964 and 1965", April, 1965
  - New Kensington, "Report on Revenue Reporting and Control City of New Kensington", February, 1962
  - New Kensington, "A Need for Checks and Balances a Fiscal Survey of the City of New Kensington", March, 1962
  - New Kensington, "Pertinent Date Relating to Proposed Administrative Unit I", August, 1961
  - New Kensington, "City of New Kensington Mid-Year Budget Review", July, 1950
  - New Kensington, "City of New Kensington Pennsylvania Comments on Proposed Sewage Disposal System", December, 1951
  - New Kensington, "Some Advantages in Mechanized Accounting Procedures for the City of New Kensington", July, 1958
  - New Kensington, "City of New Kensington Mid-Year Review 1953 Budget", August, 1953
  - New Kensington, "Preliminary Report on the 1943 Budget City of New Kensington", December, 1942
  - New Kensington, "City of New Kensington Mid-Year Review 1949 Budget", August, 1949
  - New Kensington, "A Tight Squeeze the League Reviews New Kensington's 1949 City Budget and 1948 Experience", May, 1949
  - New Kensington, "Summing up the City's Financial Picture 1948 Budget and 1949 Outlook City of New Kensington", November, 1948
  - New Kensington, "1947 Financial Operations and the 1948 Budget City of New Kensington", March, 1948
  - New Kensington, "New Kensington's 1947 Budget at Mid-Year", August, 1947
  - New Kensington, "New Kensington City Finances in 1946 and 1947", April, 1947
  - New Kensington, "Management of New Kensington's Financial Improvement Program", November, 1946
  - New Kensington, "Mid- Year Review of the 1946 Budget City of New Kensington", August, 1946
  - New Kensington, "Report on the 1946 Budget City of New Kensington", March, 1946
  - New Kensington, "City of New Kensington Financial Resources for Planning", August, 1944
  - New Kensington, "City of New Kensington 1944 Budget Study", December, 1944
  - New Kensington, "Traffic Congestion in New Kensington Some of the Contributing Causes with Suggested Remedies", August, 1946
  - New Stanton, "A Borough Proposal for the New Stanton Area", May, 1965 (Box 19)
  - Newport, "Fiscal Analysis Newport Township 1959-62", February, 1963
  - North Belle Vernon, "A Review of the Accounting System Borough of North Belle Vernon", March, 1964
  - North Braddock, "Borough of North Braddock Fiscal Analysis and Projection", December, 1966
  - North Huntingdon, "Wage and Salary Review North Huntingdon Township", August, 1964
  - North Huntingdon, "The Position of a Manager in Township Administration", February, 1961
  - North Huntingdon, "Developing and Financing a Highway Improvement Program North Huntington Township", April, 1957
  - North Strabane, "General Administrative Survey", November, 1972
  - North Union, "North Union Looks Ahead a Study of North Union Township", November, 1951
  - North Versailles, "Analysis of the Tentative 1948 Budget Estimates", March, 1948
  - North Versailles, "Financial Study of North Versailles Township 1940-1945", December, 1946
  - North Versailles, "Recommended Accounting Controls for North Versailles Township: Part I Procedure", December, 1946
  - Ohiopyle, "Preliminary Report Water and Sewerage Fiscal Feasibility Study", January, 1964
  - O'Hara, "A Financial Study Relating to the Pleasant Valley and Virginia Avenue Extension Sewer Systems", April, 1955
  - O'Hara, "Police Pension Plan Self-Administered", September, 1958
  - Ohioville, "Analysis of Insurance Protection", May, 1968
  - Oakdale, "A Report on the Accounting System Survey of the Boy's Industrial Home of Western Pennsylvania", May, 1959
  - Oakmont, "Survey and Report of the Accounting System Procedures", September, 1955
  - Penn, "Financial and Operating Review 1939-1948", February, 1950
  - Penn Hills, "A Fiscal Analysis and Projection", October, 1965
  - Penn Hills, "Municipality of Penn Hills Fiscal Analysis and Projection 1973-1981", August, 1978
  - Peters, "A Suggested Accounting System and Administrative Recommendations for the Township of Peters", June, 1966
  - Peters, "A Fiscal Analysis and Projection for the Township of Peters 1959-1970", September, 1965
  - Peters, "Fiscal Operations in Peters Township: A Review and a Reflection", August, 1966
  - Philadelphia, "Parking in Philadelphia's Neighborhoods: A Study of Policies and Standards for Residential Parking Facilities in Philadelphia", 1966
  - Philadelphia, "Preliminary Report on Philadelphia Residential Parking", August, 1962
  - Philadelphia, "Analysis of Some Aspects of Proposal for a Stadium in Northeast Philadelphia Prepared Citizens' Budget Committee", June, 1961
  - Philadelphia, "Design for a Survey of the Utilization for Manpower and Materiel in the Philadelphia City Government", June, 1962
  - Philadelphia, "Parking in Philadelphia's Neighborhoods", August, 1966
  - Philadelphia, "Philadelphia's Contracting Procedures for Public Works and Materials, Supplies and Equipment", February, 1962
  - Philadelphia, "Repair of Sanitation and Highway Equipment", December, 1947
  - Philadelphia, "History of Philadelphia's City Governments with Special Reference to the Home Rule Charter and the Educational Supplement to the Charter", February, 1972
  - Philadelphia, "Licenses Permits and Fees", October, 1946
  - Philadelphia, "Manpower Requirements of the Philadelphia Fire Department", July, 1954
  - Philadelphia, "Phila. Gen'L Hospital Admission Policies Part III Rating and Collection Procedures", September, 1958
  - Philadelphia, "Philadelphia and Constitutional Revision", September, 1960
  - Philadelphia, "Philadelphia's Capital Programming Procedures", July, 1961
  - Philadelphia, "Special Assimilation Problems of Underprivileged In-Migrants to Philadelphia", July, 1962
  - Philadelphia, "Impact of proposed 1961-1966 Capital Program on Future Debt-Service Requirements", September, 1960
  - Philadelphia, "Report of Survey on the Office of the Prothonotary for the Committee of Fifteen", December, 1948
  - Philadelphia, "Purchase Versus Renal of Punched Card Tabulating machine Equipment for Certain Work Operations", October, 1947
  - Philadelphia, "Administration of Philadelphia's Hazard Benefit Programs", March, 1959
  - Philadelphia, "Digest of the General and Specific Provisions of the Philadelphia Home Rule Charter Report No. 4", January, 1954
  - Philadelphia, "Digest of the General and Specific Provisions of the Philadelphia Home Rule Charter Report No. 15", March, 1954
  - Philadelphia, "Debt Structure and Proposed Debt Reorganization Plan", February, 1941
  - Philadelphia, "The Magistrates' Courts of Philadelphia Revised Edition", 1958
  - Philadelphia, "Report on Philadelphia Fairmont Park Guards Pensions", December, 1954
  - Philadelphia, "Sub-Committee of City Council for Reclassification Part I on Description, Findings, and Recommendations", February, 1953
  - Philadelphia, "Sub-Committee of City Council for Reclassification Part II on Classification Plan", February, 1943
  - Philadelphia, "Office and Storage Space in City Hall and City Hall Annex", November, 1951
  - Philadelphia, "Printing Shops in the City Government of Philadelphia", July, 1952 (Box 20)
  - Philadelphia, "General Hospital Admission Policies and Procedures", December, 1958
  - Philadelphia, "Philadelphia General Hospital Admission Policies Part I Description and Analysis of Admission and Rate Regulations", April, 1958
  - Philadelphia, "Phila. Gen'L Hospital Admission Polices Part III Social and Economic Date Relating to Sample of Inpatint Groups", June, 1958
  - Philadelphia, "Report of Administrative Survey of the Municipal Court of Philadelphia", December, 1948
  - Philadelphia, "Administrative Survey of the Philadelphia Department of Licenses and Inspections Volume One", December, 1956
  - Philadelphia, "Administrative Survey of the Philadelphia Department of Licenses and Inspections Volume Two", December, 1956
  - Philadelphia, "Real Property Facilities Department of Streets", June, 1954
  - Philadelphia, "Philadelphia Uniformed Forces Compensation Study", March, 1959
  - Philadelphia, "A Comparison of Fringe Benefits in City Government and Private Employment in Philadelphia", January, 1957
  - Pitcairn, "Financial Survey Borough of Pitcairn", March, 1957
  - Pittsburgh, "Section I City of Pittsburgh Financial Operating Summary 1968-1975"
  - Pittsburgh, "City of Pittsburgh Revenues – 1977"
  - Pittsburgh, "Proposed Chapter for the City of Pittsburgh", 1940
  - Pittsburgh, "Preliminary Report on the Financial and Business Administration Phases of the Bureau of Recreation", April, 1942
  - Pittsburgh, "Central Administrative Accounting System", April, 1942
  - Pittsburgh, "Recommendations on the 1943 Budget"
  - Pittsburgh, "Survey of Refuse Collection and Disposal", May, 1944
  - Pittsburgh, "External Influences and Internal Fiscal Problems Confronting the Government", October, 1944
  - Pittsburgh, "Public Authority of Pittsburgh Financial Statements September 30, 1956", December, 1956
  - Pittsburgh, "Public Authority of Pittsburgh Financial Statements September 30, 1958", December, 1958
  - Pittsburgh, "Public Authority of Pittsburgh Financial Statements September 30, 1961", November, 1961
  - Pittsburgh, "Public Authority of Pittsburgh Financial Statements September 30, 1962", December, 1962
  - Pittsburgh, "Public Authority of Pittsburgh Financial Statements September 30, 1963", December, 1963
  - Pittsburgh, "Public Authority of Pittsburgh Financial Statements September 30, 1964", November, 1964
  - Pittsburgh, "Public Authority of Pittsburgh Financial Statements September 30, 1966", November, 1966
  - Pittsburgh, "Public Authority of Pittsburgh Financial Statements September 30, 1967", December, 1967
  - Pittsburgh, "Public Authority of Pittsburgh Financial Statements September 30, 1968", November, 1968
  - Pittsburgh, "The Meter Reading Function Department of Water", August, 1972
  - Pittsburgh, "Public Authority of Pittsburgh Financial Statements September 30, 1969", January, 1970
  - Pittsburgh, "A More Effective Industrial Development Program for the Pittsburgh Region", November, 1954
  - Pittsburgh, "Projection of Financial Requirements 1955 of 1957 Pittsburgh Board of Public Education", October, 1954
  - Pittsburgh, "An Analysis of the City of Pittsburgh's Residential Real Estate Management Program", December, 1978
  - Pittsburgh, "A Management Study of the Bureau of Bridges, Highways and Sewers Department of Public Works A Survey Report 1967", August, 1967
  - Pittsburgh, "A Financial Program for Pittsburgh", 1940
  - Pittsburgh, "Parking Survey and Program Squirrel Hill Business District", May, 1956
  - Pittsburgh, "Proposed Classification and Pay Plan for Professional and Clerical Positions", July, 1962
  - Pittsburgh, "Regulating and Controlling Opening in Municipal Streets: A Model Ordinance", 1958
  - Pittsburgh, "Reports on Capital Improvement Requirements 1957-1961", July, 1956
  - Pittsburgh, "Administrative Study of the Division of Street Lighting", August, 1963 (Box 21)
  - Pittsburgh, "Administrative Study of the Public Works Inspection Division", October, 1963
  - Pittsburgh, "Public Property Inventory Project: Proposed Work Program", July, 1979
  - Pittsburgh, "Possible Sources of New Revenue", October, 1966
  - Pittsburgh, "City of Pittsburgh Evaluation of 1972 Budget", February, 1972
  - Pittsburgh, "Fiscal Analysis and Projection Borough of East Pittsburgh 1960-1971", May, 1966
  - Pittsburgh, "Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh and Carnegie Institute Position Classification and Pay Plan", February, 1976
  - Pittsburgh, "Coordinated Planning for Hospitals", February 1959
  - Pittsburgh, "Hotel, Food and Liquor Concessions at Greater Pittsburgh Airport", April, 1968
  - Pittsburgh, "A Proposed Classification and Pay Plan for City of Pittsburgh Volume I", November, 1960
  - Pittsburgh, "Appendix to Classification Manual: Forms to be used for Evaluating and Classifying Occupations for Political Subdivisions", January, 1952
  - Pittsburgh, "A Manual for Evaluation and Classification of Occupations", May, 1948
  - Pittsburgh, "A Study to Develop Techniques for the Fiscal Coordination of Community Improvements and Urban Renewal in the Pittsburgh Area", Unknown
  - Pittsburgh, "Child Caring Institutions: A Functional Analysis of Costs", June, 1968
  - Pittsburgh, "Background and Summary of Proposed New Zoning Ordinance", October, 1956
  - Pittsburgh, "Stray Animal Control Report", October, 1964
  - Pittsburgh, "A Study of Civic Agencies in the Pittsburgh Area", October, 1958
  - Pittsburgh, "An Alternative Payments Basis for the Business Privilege Tax and the Mercantile Tax", 1969
  - Pittsburgh, "The Allegheny Seminar Proceedings Municipal Police Services", May, 1968
  - Pittsburgh, "The Potential for Effective Labor-Management Relations in the Pittsburgh Region", November, 1957
  - Pittsburgh, "An Analysis of the Current Policies and Procedures Concerning the Acquisition, Management and Resale of Residential Real Estate by the City of Pittsburgh", October, 1978
  - Pittsburgh, "Preliminary Report to the First Boston Corporation, Singer, Dean and Scribner, and Moore, Leonard and Lynch upon the Water Works System", September, 1951
  - Pittsburgh, "A Study to Develop Techniques for the Fiscal Coordination of Community Improvements", January, 1965
  - Pittsburgh, "Administrative Study of the Sidewalk inspection Division, Bureau of Bridges, Highways and Sewers", August, 1963
  - Pittsburgh, "Detailed Equipment Study of the Bureau of Highways and Sewers Department of Public Work", December, 1952
  - Pittsburgh, "Proposed Salary Plan for Staff Positions of Public Parking Authority", September, 1959
  - Pittsburgh, "Volume II Statistical Appendixes and Exhibits for a Study to Develop Techniques for the Fiscal Coordination of Community Improvements and Urban Renewal in the Pittsburgh Area", November, 1965
  - Pittsburgh, "Metropolitan Pittsburgh Educational Television Preliminary Operating Cost Analysis", February, 1953
  - Pittsburgh, "Space Utilization by City of Pittsburgh in the City-County Building", December, 1952
  - Pittsburgh, "An Administrative Study of Selected Operations of the Housing Authority of the City of Pittsburgh", December, 1967
  - Pittsburgh, "A Pay-as-you-go Program", July, 1938
  - Pittsburgh, "Comments on the 1940 Budget of the City of Pittsburgh", December, 1939
  - Pittsburgh, "Urban Redevelopment Authority of Pittsburgh Position Description Position Classification and Pay Plan", December, 1982
  - Pittsburgh, "Report of the Survey of Certain Functions of the Department of Public Health", May, 1940
  - Pittsburgh, "A 25-Year Fiscal Review of City of Pittsburgh 1920 through 1944", July, 1945
  - Pittsburgh, "City of Pittsburgh Financial Operating Summary 1968-1975"
  - Pittsburgh: "Proposed New Zoning Ordinance", October, 1956
  - Pittsburgh, "Financing Date Processing Equipment in the Office of the City Treasurer", August, 1966
  - Pittsburgh, "Report on Preliminary Study for Water Waste Survey", September, 1929
  - Pittsburgh, "Analysis of 1954 Budget Requests (Excludes Salaries and Wages)"
  - Pittsburgh, "Report on the Survey of the Department of Lands and Buildings", August, 1950
  - Pittsburgh, "Recommended Improvements for Warehousing by the Department of Supplies," January, 1953
  - Pittsburgh, "Operating Study of the Bureau of Highways and Sewers Department of Public Works", September, 1952
  - Pittsburgh, "Supplemental Report on the Bureau of Water," February, 1936
  - Pittsburgh, "1944 Budget Requests Recommended Decreases and Tables", October, 1943
  - Pittsburgh, "Report on the Survey of the Bureau of Highways and Sewers", August, 1940
  - Pittsburgh, "Preliminary Report on Enforcement of Smoke Inspection", April, 1941
  - Pittsburgh, "Recommended Changes in 1945 Budget Requests"
  - Pittsburgh, "Plan for Improvement in Methods of Purchasing, Storekeeping, and Administration of Shops and Transportation", November, 1938
  - Pittsburgh, "Cost Accounting Survey Department of Public Works (Except Bureau of Water)", September, 1934
  - Pittsburgh, "Preliminary report on the Accounting Methods and procedures of the Department of the City Controller and the City Treasurer", December, 1934
  - Pittsburgh, "City of Pittsburgh-Fiscal Monitoring 1975", 1970-1975
  - Pittsburgh, "Pittsburgh Quarterly Reviews and Expenditure 1971-1976"
  - Pittsburgh, "City of Pittsburgh – Pittsburgh Fiscal trends (Adds-1976)", 1968-1975
  - Pittsburgh, "Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh and Carnegie Institute: Position Classification and Pay Plan", February, 1976
  - Pittsburgh, "Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh and Carnegie Institute: Position Classification and Pay Plan", February, 1976
  - Pittsburgh, "Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh and Carnegie Institute: Position Classification and Pay Plan", February, 1976 (Box 22)
  - Pittsburgh, "Efficiency and Economy Commission of Pittsburgh, Sub-Committee on Stores Report No. 1 General and Present Procedure", Unknown
  - Pittsburgh, "Efficiency and Economy Commission of Pittsburgh, Sub-Committee on Stores Report No. 2 Proposed Central Warehouse and Storage Yard", Unknown
  - Pittsburgh, "Efficiency and Economy Commissions of Pittsburgh, Sub-Committee on Budget and Disbursements Accounting", April, 1935
  - Pittsburgh, "Efficiency and Economy Commissions of Pittsburgh, Report of Sub-Committee on Timekeeping and Pay Roll", December, 1935
  - Pittsburgh, "Efficiency and Economy Commissions of Pittsburgh, Report on Debt and Sinking Funds", March, 1935
  - Pittsburgh, "Efficiency and Economy Commission of Pittsburgh, A Plan for a Centralized Pay Roll Procedure", July, 1935
  - Pittsburgh, "Efficiency and Economy Commission of Pittsburgh, Report on Bureau of Water", April, 1935
  - Pittsburgh, "Efficiency and economy Commission of Pittsburgh, Engineering Committee Report of Sub-Committee Bureau of Highways and Sewers", March, 1937
  - Pittsburgh, "Efficiency and Economy Commission of Pittsburgh Automotive Report Part No. 1", March, 1935
  - Pottstown, "Meeting the Pottstown Area's Future Hospital and Hospital Related Health Needs", 1964
  - Port Vue, "A Financial Analysis of Port Vue Borough", March, 1960
  - Port Vue, "Borough of Port Vue Police Pension Plan Self-Administered", July, 1958
  - Reading, "A Survey of the Streets in the City of Reading", March, 1949
  - Reading, "A Survey of City-Owned Automotive Equipment", December, 1938
  - Reading, "Possible Joint Water-Sewer Authority for Reading", August, 1954
  - Reading, "Organization of the Reading City Government as it now Exists and with Proposed Changes, Volume I of a Survey of Positions, Salaries, and Wages", November, 1942
  - Rochester, "An Area Program for a Police Radio Network", August, 1959
  - Rochester, "Police Radio Network Rochester Area", June, 1972
  - Ross, "Financial and Operating Review 1949-1959", April, 1960
  - Rosslyn Farms, "An Evaluation of the Costs of Providing Fire and Police Protection", April, 1959
  - Rostraver, "A Review of the Financial Operations and Financial Position", September, 1959
  - Republic, "A Study of Procedures and Proposals for Incorporation", November, 1962
  - Salina, "Financing a Water Supply for the Salina Water System", October, 1965
  - Scottdale, "Suggestions Relating to the Accounting System of the Borough of Scottdale", January, 1957
  - Scottdale, "Recommendations Relating to the Accounting System", January, 1961
  - Scottdale, "Survey of Parking Facilities Borough of Scottdale", July, 1966
  - Scottdale, "Study of Financial Position Borough of Scottdale 1950-1959", July, 1959
  - Scottdale, "A Study of Downtown Parking Facilities in the Borough of Scottdale", July, 1956
  - Scottdale, "Administrative and Organization Survey Borough of Scottdale", July, 1950
  - Scranton, "Analysis of Proposed 1956 Scranton City Bond Issue", March, 1956
  - Scranton, "Scranton City Government Survey of the Bureau of Fire", January, 1961
  - Scranton, "Reclassification of the City of Scranton", November, 1960
  - Scranton, "Resources for Urban Renewal", June, 1965
  - Sewickley, "A Study of Sewickley Township Report I Financial Operating Experience and Outlook", May, 1960
  - Sewickley, "The Sewickley Bridge a Critical Link", October, 1977
  - Sewickley, "A Financial Plan for Sewickley Township", January, 1944
  - Shanon, "New Public Library/Parking Facility an Analysis of Cost, Size, and Financing Methods", July, 1969
  - Shanon, "City of Shanon Numerical Codification Manual", April, 1972
  - Shanon, "A Study of Garbage Disposal Practices for City of Sharon", April, 1953
  - Shanon, "Position Classification of Non-Uniformed Personnel", February, 1977
  - Shanon, "A Report on the Public Transportation Problem in the Shenango Valley", November, 1958
  - Shanon, "Report on Sewage treatment Facilities", June, 1958 (Box 23)
  - Shanon, "A Report on the Advisability of Supplementing the Paid Fire Department of the City of Sharon with Volunteers", March, 1955
  - Sharon, "Sharon – A City in Transition a Report Recommending Changes Necessary for the Establishment of a Strong Mayor Form of Government", September, 1961
  - Sharon, "A Review of the 1946 Expenditures and the 1946 Budget", February, 1947
  - Sharon, "A Coordinated Plan for Hospital Improvement", March, 1960
  - Sharon, "An Analysis of the 1946 Budgets", January, 1946
  - Sharon, "A Study to Determine the Advisability of Establishing a Valley-Wide System of Refuse Collection and/or Disposal", May, 1957
  - Sharon, "Preliminary Financial Analysis 1939 to 1944 Inclusive", May, 1945
  - Sharon, "A Proposed Position Classification Plan for all Non-Professional Employees of Sharon School District", March, 1962
  - Sharon, "A Review of Financial Trends City of Sharon 1933-1945 Supplemented with 1946 Possibilities", May, 1946
  - Sharon, "Sharon's Redevelopment Program – an Evaluation", December, 1965
  - Sharon, "A Twenty-Five Year Financial Program for Sharon", June, 1946
  - Sharon, "Memorandum on Sewage Treatment Plant Improvements", August, 1958
  - Sharon, "Municipal Employees' Retirement System", May, 1961
  - Sharpsburg, "Electric Plant Study an Analysis of the Fiscal Impact of Electric Plant Proposals under Consideration by Borough of Sharpsburg", September, 1962
  - Sharpsburg, "Financial and Operating Study", December, 1951
  - Sharpsburg, "Borough of Sharpsburg Police Pension Fund", May, 1960
  - Sharpsville, "Fiscal Analysis and Projection 1975-1983", October, 1980
  - Sharpsville, "$110,000 of Bonds Series of September, 1957 to be Offered for Sale Monday, August 12, 1957 – 7:30pm"
  - Sharpsville, "$215,000 of Bonds Series of February, 1960 to be Offered for Sale Thursday, January 28, 1960-7:30pm, est."
  - Sharpsville, "Memorandum on Sewage Treatment Plant Improvements", August, 1958
  - Sharpsville, "A Recommended Position Classification Plan", October, 1962
  - Sharpsville, "A Self-Administered Pension Plan for Fire Department Employees", January, 1961
  - Sharpsville, "A Financial Analysis of the Borough of Sharpsville 1941-1949 and Tentative Budet for 1950", March, 1950
  - Sharpsville, "Accounting System Survey and Recommendations", March, 1956
  - Sharpsville, "Report Upon Sewage Treatment Facilities", April, 1958
  - Sharpsville, "The Financial Impact of the Proposed Bond Issue", October, 1955
  - Sharpsville, "Memorandum on Sewage Treatment Plant Improvements", August,1958
  - Sharpsville, "An Operating Study of the Department", September, 1950
  - Shenango Valley, "An Economic Base Survey of the Shenango Valley Area and Mercer County," (Copy in Folder), November, 1956